It's my life, it's your life, fighting for
tomorrow, go catch what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life, run
like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong, believe
you can achieve your call.
Let's keep on going, I'll not stay.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
No one can make my dream come true?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only wait out.
We can let go together,
baby, crawling around.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your light.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
You're talking?
Since when can you speak?
Always could.
You mean...
you've lied to your
brother this whole time?
I never once indicated to
him that I became mute.
That is a crazy assumption
the guy made on his own.
You're being deceitful!
Why not correcting me?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Silence now.
Huh?
Oh, the sound stopped. Where'd it go?
How?
It looks like people are talking,
but I can't hear anything.
You were being loud, so
I took a countermeasure.
They can't hear us.
Just like how you can't
hear a peep from outside.
I put up a soundproof wall to cover us.
I ate the calm calm fruit
and became a silent man.
You have Devil Fruit powers.
You're insane.
It's all for a lie.
Wait a sec.
You faked the accidents too, didn't you?
That's right.
You're a sharp cookie.
The whole klutz thing is an act.
You caught on fire again, you liar!
I've been clumsy my whole life.
That won't change.
There, you happy now?
Give me a break!
You mean to tell me that's
the only truth to you?
Why are you hiding all this
crap from your friends?
They're not my friends.
I'm with them.
But not by choice.
Someone's gotta curb my
brother Duffy's rampage.
It's hard to believe we're related.
Our parents showed us
nothing but love, after all.
But that monster has no humanity.
Help me!
Please, my boys are innocent!
Director, how is it made of them?
I beg you, please don't
harm my children anymore.
Help, Daddy.
It hurts everywhere.
I want to die.
I'll get even.
I swear it.
Sophie, no.
You wretches!
I won't die today.
I swear to survive whatever
torment you throw at me!
Remember my words!
I look forward to the day that I hunt you
down and murder every single one of you!
He's dangerous.
My brother's innately wicked
nature knows no bounds.
The only people who have seen
the full extent of his brutality
are the four executives, including
me and the first Corazon, Vergo.
Who's Vergo?
An extremely powerful individual.
Right now, he's away from the
family on a secret operation.
But the details of that
are between him and Duffy.
That guy has nothing to do
with you, so forget about him.
You can't turn into a
monster like my brother.
Now scram, quickly. No
way! I'm not leaving!
That's exactly what I want to be!
Look, you possess the secret name of D.
You realize what that means?
You're part of a fateful few.
Growing up, when children
misbehaved, we were told,
if you don't fall in line,
you'll be eaten alive by D.
Every so often, another person with D in
their name would gain public attention.
You'd overhear the elderly
making passing comments like,
D will surely bring a new storm.
The hell's that mean?
You trying to say I'm a monster, then?
Perhaps.
The details are still unknown, but
that name survived for centuries,
and has been muttered
across the entire world.
One more thing.
Those who fear the inheritors of
D have given them another title.
Sworn enemy of gods.
Gods?
If celestial dragons are
gods in this analogy,
the purpose of your people might
be the destruction of this world.
But look, this meaning of
destruction is different than Dofis.
It's a force that opposes
the order of heaven itself.
Why are you spouting this crap at me?!
I joined your dumb family for one purpose!
To kill people before I die!
Don't assume I want to work for you!
I only answer to Doflamingo!
What would I want to leave for?
I'm just gonna die in a year anyway!
There's gotta be a cure out
there somewhere. Shut up!
I'm so ready, you're out! Sucker!
Doflamingo will be angry!
Hey, wait!
Bet he freaks out when
he learns you can talk!
You damn brat!
I'm way stronger than two years ago.
Later, jerk!
You moron!
You broke the blood law a second time!
Hey, why were you moving your
mouths but not saying anything?
I'll buy you both ice cream
if you shut up about it.
Really?
I'll take a 500-berry king-size cone.
Baby Five, can you spot me?
Huh? Okay.
Oh, my gosh.
He really needs me for something.
My time's up.
Damn it.
I shouldn't have trusted that kid.
I screwed up royally.
Corazon, we're about to set sail.
The Navy's on our tail again.
Zuru's on our way.
We gotta go.
Hasn't he said anything yet?
I decided not to tell.
I gave it some thought.
And remembered that I owed you for
keeping quiet back when I stabbed you.
I'd call that about even.
Anyone seen Ham or Law? What?
I swear I saw them board
together. They aren't here?
We need the extra firepower
and can't find either of them.
And I looked everywhere.
Young Master, found this
in Corazon's hammock.
Looks like they took off together.
What the hell is he thinking?
Un-tie me right now!
Hey, pick up that transponder still!
It's Joe Flamingo, isn't it?
I'll talk, just pick it up!
Come on, pick it up!
What's wrong with you?
Joe Flamingo, help!
What are you gonna do to me?
What are you calling up?
Hey, come and rescue me!
Rice crackers Cookies, it's me.
Oh brucinante.
Hey, uh, need some time off?
You run into trouble—it's
a personal matter.
I see, understood?
How are the little ones doing?
Think you can scare them off soon?
I think those three are staying.
That
family is becoming infamous
now—take extra caution!
extra caution
Do as you see fit.
I wholeheartedly entrust this case to you.
Just keep me updated.
Roger that.
I'll send you a detailed report.
Admiral Sengoku!
The officer who asked
for reassignment is here.
Yes, yes, send him in.
You wanted to see me?
I've heard a lot about you.
You've had quite a successful first year
and have been turning a lot of heads.
You wish to transfer to G5, correct?
What was your name again?
Also, FYI, there's half
an egg on your cheek.
Sir, name's Vergo.
Who'd you call just now?
Did you say report?
You've been hiding something?
Were you working with the Navy?
Got something against him?
The government and their allies sicken me!
Well, I ain't no Marine.
Is that a lie?
I won't go to the hospital!
You're acting like every
other brat in the world, Law.
I'll go to every hospital if I have to.
I'll find a cure for your sickness.
Look how big this one is.
I bet they can fix you up.
Get that kid out of here!
You can't catch white lead disease.
Isn't there any medicine for it yet?
M-m-might I ask?
Where were you born?
I'm from Flevance.
That's the White Town!
No!
I don't want to get sick! Get it together!
We need anticeptic gloves and a gas mask!
Call security and notify
the government! Trotto!
No! No! Forget it!
Law!
See that?
I'm subhuman to them!
Please leave us alone, you white monster.
We don't want your gross disease.
How dare you bring that infected little
creature into a hospital of all places?
Do you realize you're putting
hundreds of patients at risk?
This is an emergency announcement.
A patient with white lead
disease is loose in the hospital.
Get me back!
What a dangerous freak!
All wards, prepare for sterilization.
Forget that hospital.
I'm real sorry.
Hope that didn't hit a
sore spot on you, kid.
I told you!
I didn't want to see a doctor!
Not all doctors suck like him.
I'm positive we'll find a good
one at this next hospital.
Don't force me to go!
He should be put down!
That's a severe case of
that white lead disease!
Take him away before he dooms us all!
Change of plans.
Let's try the next one.
Enough!
I'm tired of this!
We've got an emergency! Help!
There's a flooded survivor!
You were supposed to purge them all!
Look, all the people around
here seem kind-hearted!
No!
Take those filthy white
blotches away from us!
Screw you, buddy!
Eight hospitals have been hit as a boy
with white lead disease terrorizes...
I'm getting sicker.
I can't take anymore.
Shut up.
You'll find the cure.
You're not gonna die.
This next one will help you.
Don't give up.
White lead disease!
Put the hospital on lockdown!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
This kiddo needs your help!
I've had enough!
Corazon!
What the hell am I doing?
I've been forcing this poor kid to relive
his horrible childhood
over and over again.
He's not getting any better either.
I wondered if it was the
Will of D driving me.
No, I don't care about that anymore.
I just...
I just feel so sorry for this damn kid.
Knowing you.
You'd hate to hear this,
but this blubbering idiot is trying
everything he can to save you.
You're still a pain in the ass kid,
but hearing you talk about death—my
heart can't take it.
You may have stabbed me,
you little shit! But?
but
It didn't hurt at all.
You were the one who was
actually suffering back then.
I just wanted to fix things for you, Mom.
Cora!
Hey, Cora!
Breakfast is done!
What's that face for?
You called me Cora?
You said that, yeah?
You want the food or not?
Cora's own. It's me.
What's wrong?
I know you're there.
It's already been six months
since you took off on your own.
Is law still with you?
Doflamingo.
I see.
Well, I'm glad both of you are all right.
Have you found a good doctor?
I had a feeling.
I think it's time you
come back to the ship.
We might be able to cure Law's disease.
I happen to find a lead
on the op-op fruit.
Some stupid pirates who don't know
what it's worth got their hands on it.
Seems the Navy caught wind,
because now they're offering them a ton
of money and getting ready for trade.
As usual, the world government is
pulling strings to get their way.
It's risky, but we can steal it.
Once we have it,
due to the nature of its power,
I can only allow someone whose
loyalty I trust completely to eat it.
And that would be you, Corazon.
Afterwards, you can cure Law's disease.
What do you think?
I value your opinion.
The Navy has been hounding us
everywhere we went quite consistently.
Saru, in particular,
always seemed to find us.
But in the past six months,
the Navy hasn't reared its
ugly head around us even once.
You'll note, that's exactly
how long Corazon's been gone.
You think your dear little brother has
been tipping off the Navy this whole time?
Could be a coincidence, though.
That's certainly what I'm hoping.
I don't want to distrust him, honestly.
We're still family after all.
Look at your law.
Forget those stupid
doctors—you're gonna make
it without them once
we get the op op fruit.
Your white lead disease
will be a thing of the past.
What's the op op fruit? Do it.
Lets you modify someone's body.
You can perform miracle operations
and cure any nasty diseases.
diseases
Yeah, right.
I don't believe in fairy tales.
It's real.
But there's a catch.
You need knowledge to use it.
But that's no problem.
Because I know you're the
son of a brilliant doctor.
One who was trusted by
the people of Flevins.
But why does that matter now?
Are you kidding?
It matters because you're
going to eat the fruit.
I am?
Don't Flamingo said you were
supposed to eat it, though.
A person will die if he
eats two devil fruits.
Duffy only said that because he doesn't
know about my calm, calm fruit-ability.
We're through with Duffy.
We aren't going back to the family.
That decision became clear to me
as my journey with you dragged on.
By now, I'm sure Duffy has
realized that I'm a traitor
Uh, are you sure?
On this snail, he said you
should eat the fruit, right?
There is a secondary reason
behind that decision.
It has nothing to do with trust.
I get it, Duffy!
You want me to sacrifice myself
to give you eternal life!
And if I don't, I'm a traitor!
But either way, I'm dead.
Listen, we'll get the jump on Dofi.
We'll steal the Op-Op fruit
before anybody else can have it.
You'll eat the fruit
and cure your illness.
When you're better, we can go
into hiding somewhere together.
Prepare to set sail.
We'll get that fruit,
no matter what it takes.
Garlic.
Rice crackers!
Cookies. It's me.
Rosanante, it's been a while.
I've been worried about you.
Hey, Garp, could you step
out for a second? What? Why?
I just brought you snacks, didn't I?
At least offer me some tea.
Bye, Admiral Garp.
Is now a bad time to chat, Sengoku?
Make your own damn tea.
I got work to do.
Now get out of here, you fool.
Shoo, shoo.
Yeah,
well, I'm taking the rest of the snacks
with me if that's how you're going to act.
Um, can I talk now?
Yeah, sorry. Go ahead.
I heard you were looking to make
a trade for the op-op fruit.
Yes, but how did you know that?
My brother caught wind of it somehow.
What?
That's top secret info.
I see.
So that's who you're talking to, huh?
Where can I find the pirates
you're making the trade with?
I don't know.
If they're smart, they're
laying low right now.
And what if I told you that Doflamingo was
going to steal the fruit
before you could buy it?
Is he?
Weird.
I'm dizzy all of a sudden.
When and where are you making the trade?
Three weeks from now at
Rubeck in the North Blue.
Rubeck.
I'll meet Dofie and his
friends on Swallow Island.
They should be there three days
before the handoff happens.
That's where you'll be waiting?
I imagine he won't want
to take any chances,
so he'll likely bring the
entire family with him.
Thanks for the intel.
So we'll plan an ambush at Swallow Island.
That'll be the end of Doflamingo.
It's a chance to catch the whole Don
Quixote family in one fell swoop.
Just make sure you stay away.
That was the plan.
I've got a list I'll
be sending your way as
soon as I can of Dofie's
business partners.
Big shots working behind the scenes.
Bunch of dark little secrets
hiding there in the north.
Blue, I see, thank you.
Gotta lick!
Hey, law!
You ready to take off?
Gotta move.
Are you okay?
Come on, kid.
Stay with me!
Not now.
When we finally have a real chance to
save you, it hasn't been three years yet?
You said you had more time than this.
You gotta hang in there.
Oh, jeez, the fever's bad.
What should I do?
Doctors are useless.
It's all up to me now to save him.
What am I supposed to do, Law?
Give me a hint, please!
You gotta pull through this, okay?
Just stay alive for three more weeks.
Give me a chance to make this right!
Damn it!
Why did a storm have to hit now?
Couran.
Huh?
What's wrong, Ra?
All those years, the government
knew that my people would die.
but they kept making us take
up that white land to get rich.
The people of Lovitz and my family,
the government?
killed them.
Tell me the truth.
Are you one of them working with the navy?
Are you a marine like the others?
You're kidding me?
No, I could never be a marine.
What a relief!
I'm with you, law, but listen to me, okay.
Once you and I run away
with the up up fruit,
we'll make enemies of everyone—doflamingo
the navy and the world
government—and they'll chase us to
the end of the world if they have to,
so if you want to live, be
prepared to fight for it.
Any update
on the location of those pirates, sengoku?
Yeah, they're hiding in a ghost town.
In this place called
minion island—it's right to
the east of rubeck—where
they're making the trade.
they're making the trade
Seems like they have a hideout over there.
The pirate's name is Diaz Barrels.
That ring a bell?
Yeah, he's a former Navy officer, right?
Good memory.
Anyway, our lookout ship is
monitoring Minion Island as we speak.
Everything he said seems to check out.
We have everything set up
at Swallow Island, too.
Near where you told Doflamingo
you were gonna meet him.
We brought two warships to deal with him.
We're ready for an Alto battle.
I won't let Doe Flamingo get his
grubby fingers on the op-op fruit,
no matter what it takes.
Okay.
It won't be long now, Law.
Wait here.
Mr.
EA, where's my booze?
I need a refill!
Right away.
All this money for one fruit!
You know how much they offered us, huh?
Five billion berries, man!
What a bunch of suckers!
Is the government full of morons or what?
If we get that much money, we don't
even need to be pirates anymore!
We can just stuff our faces and party!
Yeah, that sounds good to me!
From what I understand about this thing,
if a doctor gobbles it up,
then he'll get the skills to be a
world-famous surgeon like none other.
There was some legendary doctor
who ate it some time ago.
They say he could perform
miracles with a scalpel,
cure incurable diseases,
that sort of thing.
But what the hell do I care?
I don't need to be a surgeon.
Not when you're as rich as we're gonna be.
Damn straight!
check this out law everything that's near
me won't make a peep after i do this calm
The face.
Ugh, that stinks!
Just like magic!
You didn't hear a thing, did you?
Who cares?
What the hell is that even good for?
It's totally dumb!
BB-5's arms-arms power is way cool!
Yeah, you're right!
I totally wish I could do that stuff, too!
But when it comes to having a peaceful
night's sleep, no one beats me!
What?
What happened? An earthquake?
Captain!
I didn't hear an explosion,
but something blew up!
The coal pole's on fire! What?
Was there an explosion or not?
My treasure!
My treasure's running!
Put out the fire already!
What's going on here?
We must be under attack somehow, huh?
The lights just went out.
Where's all this glass
coming from? The lamps!
They were all shattered!
Somebody, light a candle, would you?
Come on!
Doesn't anybody have a light?
I got it, Law.
Just like I said I would.
We're going to cure that
disease of yours right up.
That freaked me out.
Who's that?
He fell out of nowhere.
Hey!
The guy in a black coat just stole the
all-bought fruit and he was coming this way!
Don't let him escape!
It's him!
I know you've got it, Ruff.
But wait for me here, okay?
I'll be back, and I'll have
the Arpuffroot with me too.